It was driven by all our core geographies.
You can see here in the middle panel,
U.S. weekly TRX reached another record high.
That 25% growth was fueled by consistent demand
across the various segments that we competed.
Outside of the U.S., growth was 30%,
with strong contribution from China and Japan,
where we continue to see momentum from Entresto in heart failure,
but importantly as well in hypertension.
So we remain confident in the continued sustained performance of the medicine.
For forecasting purposes, we continue to assume an Entresto LOE in mid-2025.
However, we continue to enforce our patents and litigate our patents
and will ensure that we maximize this brand for as long as possible in the United States,
alongside EU RDP in November of 2026.
Then moving to slide seven,
Cosentix grew at 22% in the quarter,
and this is fueled by our new launches.
And I think importantly, if you take a step back,
puts us well on our trajectory to reach $7 billion plus peak sales for Cosentix.
When you look at the demand growth by geography,
the U.S. grew 34%, driven by volume.
Ex-U.S., we were up 10%.
And this was partially offset by one-time pricing effects
due in Germany in particular,
due to the addition of additional new indication,
normal part of the German process.
As you get additional indications, you do see price adjustments.
We see Cosentix doing very well in its core indications.
I think one important dynamic is the strong launch in HS
is supporting us in our core indications of psoriasis, PSA, and AS.
We're the number one IL-17 in the U.S. dynamic market,
the lead originator biologic in Europe and China.
In HS, we're seeing a very strong uptake with market leadership,
a share over 60% in the NBRX.
In Germany, we're over 50%.
And I think importantly, with the launch of Cosentix,
we're seeing increased diagnosis and desire to treat
amongst physicians and patients,
which I think will allow the HS market to grow
to larger than it's historically been.
And of course, allow Cosentix to help these patients
achieve their treatment goals.
For Cosentix IV, we saw solid adoption
with over 700 accounts now ordering.
And we do expect further demand increases in the second half
now that we have a permanent,
day code in effect as of July 1.
So moving to slide A,
Cosentix also delivered, as I mentioned,
a very strong quarter two, 65% growth.
This was broad-based in terms of its geographic growth profile.
Over 100,000 patients have now been treated worldwide,
naive or first switch with Cosentix.
In the U.S., we saw 49% growth.
This demand growth was driven by TRX volume of 43%
versus prior year.
We gained.
We have a 34% market share overall in segments.
Outside of the U.S., we have NBRX leadership
in seven out of 10 major markets.
So looking forward, we feel confident we will exceed
our Cosentix $4 billion guidance, peak sales guidance.
We see strong trajectory for this brand.
Its profile is unique,
self-administered B cell treatment option,
one minute a month dosing, no steroid pretreatment required,
an attractive safety profile with respect
to injection site reactions, persistence and adherence.
We're seeing in the real world setting is comparable
to infuse B cell therapies.
We also continue to generate data
which support the strong efficacy profile of this medicine.
To move to slide nine, Cascalli grew 50%
in the metastatic setting with now leading
or continued leading NBRX share in the U.S. and ex-U.S.
As you know, Cascalli has an outstanding data profile
in the metastatic breast cancer setting.
That's really supporting us consistently now.